Guide to the Committee of 100 on the Federal City records [Part I], 1932-2003 MS2017
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Subject/Issues files, 1954-1998; MS2017 Series 6
  - Historic Preservation: Cleveland Park Historical Society, "By Laws and Articles of Incorporation,", 1985 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Historic Preservation: Cleveland Park Historical Society, "Grant Project,", 1987 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Historic Preservation: Correspondence, general, 1959-1983 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Historic Preservation: Correspondence, general, 1984-1987 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Historic Preservation: Correspondence, general, March July, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Historic Preservation: Correspondence, general, August December, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Historic Preservation: Downtown Historic District, Legislation, 1973-1981 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Historic Preservation: Dumbarton Oaks, correspondence, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Historic Preservation: Dumbarton Oaks, miscellaneous statements and pamphlet, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Historic Preservation: Dumbarton Oaks, news clippings, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Historic Preservation: Dumbarton Oaks, Photographs of Garden, undated (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Historic Preservation: "Economic Benefits," pamphlet, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Historic Preservation: "F Street Club," correspondence, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Historic Preservation: "Ford Plant in Alexandria,", 1988-1989 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Historic Preservation: "G Street Remnants Building Site,", 1988-1990 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Historic Preservation: Gallinger Hospital Case, Archaeological Report, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Historic Preservation: Gallinger Hospital Case, Exhibits 1-5, 1988-1989 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Historic Preservation: Gallinger Hospital Case, Exhibits 6-11, 1987-1988 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Historic Preservation: Gallinger Hospital Case, Exhibits 13-16, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Historic Preservation: Gallinger Hospital Case, Exhibit 17, 1986-1989 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Historic Preservation: Gallinger Hospital Case, Exhibits 18-19, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Historic Preservation: Gallinger Hospital/Prison, correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Historic Preservation: Georgetown Heating and Cooling Plant, correspondence, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Historic Preservation: Georgetown Waterfront, correspondence, 1971-1975 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Historic Preservation: Georgetown Waterfront, correspondence, 1976-1981 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Historic Preservation: Georgetown Waterfront, lawsuits, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Historic Preservation: "Georgetown Waterfront Feasibility Study,", 1970 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Historic Preservation: Georgetown Waterfront Reports, 1971-1972 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Historic Preservation: Glover Archbold Park, correspondence, 1960-1978 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Historic Preservation: Glover Archbold Park, Hillendale correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Historic Preservation: Glover Archbold Park, "Hillendale Plan,", 1979 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Historic Preservation: Glover Archbold Park, news clippings, 1967 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Historic Preservation: Greyhound Bus Terminal, 1986-1991 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Historic Preservation: Greystone Mansion/Pine Crest Manor (PIPA), 1988-1989 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Historic Preservation: "The Highwaymen," pamphlet, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Historic Preservation: Historic Landmark and Historic District Act of, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Historic Preservation: Historic Landmark Acts of 1981 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Historic Preservation: "Hospital for Sick Children,", 1990 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Historic Preservation: "Justin Smith Morrill Building (Annex 3),", 1988 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Historic Preservation: Dorn McGrath's Correspondence, January March, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Historic Preservation: Dorn McGrath's Correspondence, April June, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Historic Preservation: Dorn McGrath's Correspondence, July December, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Historic Preservation: "National Postal History Museum Proposal,", 1987 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Historic Preservation: News Clippings, miscellaneous, 1963-1980 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Historic Preservation: Old Post Office, "Don't Tear It Down" and other pamphlets, undated (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Don't Tear It Down: A citizen's action group working to protect, preserve and enhance Washington's architectural environment, undated; Item 1
  - Historic Preservation: Old Post Office, NCPC Material, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Historic Preservation: Review Board Reports, June, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Historic Preservation: Rhodes Tavern, correspondence and articles, 1981-1982 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Historic Preservation: Smithsonian Five Year Plan, FY, 1986-1990 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Historic Preservation: Smithsonian Quadrangle, correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Historic Preservation: Smithsonian Quadrangle, Environmental Report, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Historic Preservation: Smithsonian Quadrangle, news clippings, 1980-1981 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Historic Preservation: Smithsonian Quadrangle, South Courtyard Report, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Historic Preservation: Miscellaneous Statements/Resolutions/Testimonies, 1966-1981 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Historic Preservation: Supreme Court Case on Landmarks Law, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Historic Preservation: Tregaron Development Material, February May, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Historic Preservation: Tregaron Development Material, June December, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Historic Preservation: Tregaron Development Material, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Historic Preservation: Tregaron Development Material, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Historic Preservation: "2000 Penn. Development," GWU Plans, 1980-1981 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Historic Preservation: "2000 Penn. Development," testimony, 1980-1981 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Historic Preservation: "Washington Preservation Conference," April, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Historic Preservation: U.S. Capitol, correspondence, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Historic Preservation: Woodward Building Project, Mayoral Agent Hearing, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Historic Preservation: Woodward Building Project, miscellaneous material, 1986-1988 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Historic Preservation: Woodward Building Project, news clippings, 1986-1987 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Transportation: "Central Washington Design Study,", 1977 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Transportation: "Civilian Control Reports,", 1967 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Transportation: Committee Reports and Recommendations, 1966-1971 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Transportation: Copies of Congressional Records and Bills, 1968-1969 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Transportation: Copies of Congressional Records and Bills, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Transportation: Dulles and National Airports, miscellaneous material, 1966-1976 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Transportation: Dulles and National Airports, miscellaneous material, 1977-1982 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Transportation: Metrorail, "NCTA Acts,", 1960-1965 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Transportation: Metrorail, news clippings, 1963-1971 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Transportation: Metrorail, press releases, 1968-1970 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Transportation: Metrorail, miscellaneous Reports and Surveys, 1968-1969 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Transportation: Metrorail. "User Reports and News Clippings,", 1979-1981 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Transportation: NCPC Comprehensive 1985 Plan, correspondence and reports, 1965-1967 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Transportation: "1985 Transportation Forecast,", 1964-1966 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Transportation: NVTC Newsletter, 1965-1966 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Transportation: Planning Board, correspondence, 1964-1971 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Transportation: Rapid Transit Planning, miscellaneous materials, 1962-1970 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Transportation: Rush Hour Statistics, undated (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Transportation: "Report on Rush Hour Travel,", 1970 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Transportation: "Transportation System and Expansion,", 1960 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Transportation: "Urban Mass Transportation Act of 1961," (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Transportation: Urban Renewal, "New Jersey Avenue,", 1970-1977 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Transportation: WMATA, Metrorail correspondence, 1971-1978 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Transportation: WMATA, Metrorail Development, 1963-1972 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Transportation: WMATA, Metrorail Funding, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Transportation: WMATA (and NCTA), Metrorail Proposals, 1960-1970 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Transportation: WMATA, Metrorail Publications and Proposals, 1967-1973 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Transportation: WMATA, News Releases and Metro Memo's, 1967-1968 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Transportation: WMATA, "Traffic Analysis Report,", 1967-1968 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Transportation, Highways: D.C. Freeway Case, Vol. I Files 1 6, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Transportation, Highways: D.C. Freeway Case, Vol. II Files 7 13, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Transportation, Highways: D.C. Freeway Case, Vol. III Files 14 23, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Transportation, Highways: D.C. Freeway Case, Vol. IV Files 24 37, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Transportation, Highways: D.C. Freeway Case, Civil Action Case 3174, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Transportation, Highways: D.C. Freeway Case, correspondence, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Transportation, Highways: D.C. Freeway Case, Memorandum and Summary Judgement, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - South Leg: "Combined Corridor and Design Report,", 1973 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - South Leg: Conservation Concerns, 1970-1973 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - South Leg: Correspondence, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - South Leg: Correspondence, June, 1973-1974 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - South Leg: Environmental Impact Study, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - South Leg: Hearing Information and Reports, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - South Leg: Hearing Statements, 1963-1972 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - South Leg: Legislative History, 1963-1971 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - South Leg: News Clippings, 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - South Leg: Report of City Council, 1970-1973 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Three Sisters Bridge: Analysis Reports, 1963-1971 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Three Sisters Bridge: Budget and Funding, 1962-1976 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Three Sisters Bridge: Chronological Notes, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Three Sisters Bridge: "The Concrete Invasion,", 1970 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Three Sisters Bridge: Constructed Files 1-12, 1962-1967 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Three Sisters Bridge: Correspondence, miscellaneous, 1962-1973 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Three Sisters Bridge: Environmental Issues, 1970-1971 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Three Sisters Bridge: Lawsuit Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Three Sisters Bridge: Lawsuit Correspondence, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Three Sisters Bridge: "Lawsuit Correspondence, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Three Sisters Bridge: Lawsuit Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Three Sisters Bridge: Legal Issues/Trial Information, 1966-1971 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Three Sisters Bridge: Miscellaneous Material, 1964-1971 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Three Sisters Bridge: News Clippings, 1966-1972 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Three Sisters Bridge: Preservation/Conservation, 1963-1968 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Three Sisters Bridge: Problems and Opposition, correspondence, 1960-1965 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Three Sisters Bridge: Problems and Opposition, correspondence, 1966-1972 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Volpe Trial: Application for Court Bond, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Volpe Trial: Congressional Record, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Volpe Trial: Court of Appeals, Vol. I Files 1-14, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Volpe Trial: Court of Appeals, Vol. I Files 15-23, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Volpe Trial: Court of Appeals, Vol. I Files 24-30, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Volpe Trial: Court of Appeals, Vol. I Files 31-40, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Volpe Trial: Court of Appeals, Vol. III Files 41-46, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Volpe Trial: Court of Appeals, Vol. III Files 47-52, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Volpe Trial: Court of Appeals, Vol. IV Files 53-68, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Volpe Trial: Court of Appeals, Vol. IV Files 69-71, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Volpe Trial: District Court, Vol. I Files 1 18a, 1969 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Volpe Trial: District Court, Vol. II Files 18b-28b, 1969 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Volpe Trial: District Court, Vol. III Files 28c-44, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Volpe Trial: District Court, Vol. III Files 45-60a, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Volpe Trial: District Court, Vol. IV Files 60b-68b, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Volpe Trial: District Court, Vol. IV-Files 69-82, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Volpe Trial: District Court. Vol. V Files 1-3, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Transportation, Highways: "Action Plan", 1973 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Transportation, Highways: Budget and User Publication, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Transportation, Highways: "Freeway Analysis and Crisis in D.C.,", 1967-1972 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Transportation, Highways: B W and GW Parkway Extension, correspondence and reports, 1969-1978 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Transportation, Highways: Chronological File, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Transportation, Highways: Chronological File, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Transportation, Highways: Chronological File, 1972-1973 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Transportation, Highways: City Council Report on D.C. Highways, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Transportation, Highways: Committee Report and Testimony on Restudying D.C. Freeways, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Transportation, Highways: Comprehensive Planning and Crisis Materials, 1966-1970 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Transportation, Highways: Congressional Bill S.728, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Transportation, Highways: Conservation Concerns, 1966-1977 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Transportation, Highways: Controversy on D.C. Freeway Projects, 1972-1973 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Transportation, Highways: Expressways Limited, correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Transportation, Highways: Federal Aid Highway Act of 1968, copies of Congressional Bills (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Transportation, Highways: Federal Aid Highway Act of 1968, correspondence (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Transportation, Highways: Federal Aid Highway Act of 1969, news clippings (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Transportation, Highways: Federal Aid Highway Act of 1968, Problems and Alternatives (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Transportation, Highways: Federal Aid Highway Act of 1968, Procedures following Introduction (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Transportation, Highways: Federal Aid Highway Act of 1970 and, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Transportation, Highways: Federal Aid Highway Act of 1970, copies of Congressional Bills (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Transportation, Highways: Freeway Airspace, Congressional Bills, 1967-1970 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Transportation, Highways: Freeway Airspace, miscellaneous material, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Transportation, Highways: Freeway Correspondence, 1962-1965 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Transportation, Highways: Freeway Correspondence, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Transportation, Highways: Freeway Correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Transportation, Highways: Freeway Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Transportation, Highways: Freeway Correspondence, 1972-1976 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Transportation, Highways: Freeway Crisis in Washington Constructed File, 1957-1966 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Transportation, Highways: Freeway Crisis in Washington, Vol. I, 1960-1963 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Transportation, Highways: Freeway Crisis in Washington, Vol. II, 1963-1965 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Transportation, Highways: Freeway Crisis in Washington, Vol. III, 1966-1967 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Transportation, Highways: Freeway Crisis in Washington, news clippings, undated (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Transportation, Highways: Freeway Maps, D.C. and Northern Virginia, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Transportation, Highways: Funding of Highway Projects, 1956-1972 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Transportation, Highways: "General Expansion," Address Lists, 1957 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Transportation, Highways: "General Expansion," Transit Reports, 1959-1960 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Transportation, Highways: I-66, Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Transportation, Highways: I-66, Correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Transportation, Highways: I-66, Correspondence, 1977-1979 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Transportation, Highways: I-66, Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Transportation, Highways: I-66, "Pamphlets, Press Releases and News Clippings,", 1970-1974 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Transportation, Highways: I-66, Reports and Testimony, 1970-1978 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Transportation, Highways: I-95, Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Transportation, Highways: I-266 Design Hearings, Agenda, 1970 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Transportation, Highways: I-266 Design Hearings, Agenda, 1970-1971 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Transportation, Highways: I-266 Design Hearings, "Environmental System Laboratory Report,", 1970 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Transportation, Highways: I-266 Design Hearings, "Peter Craig's case,", 1970 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Transportation, Highways: I-266 Design Hearings, Publications, 1970 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Transportation, Highways: I-295 (East Leg), Court Reports, 1970 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Transportation, Highways: I-295 (East Leg), Court Reports, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Transportation, Highways: I-295 (East Leg), Press Release, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Transportation, Highways: Interstate System Design Maps, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Transportation, Highways: NAS-"Highway Corridor Planning and Land Acquisition", 1967 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Transportation, Highways: National Capital Freeways Limited, "Concrete Shortcuts,", 1968 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Transportation, Highways: National Capital Freeways Limited, correspondence, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Transportation, Highways: National Capital Freeways Limited, Letterhead and Notes, undated (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Transportation, Highways: News Clippings, Miscellaneous, 1967-1971 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Transportation, Highways: 1969 Freeway Lawsuit, correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Transportation, Highways: 1969 Freeway Lawsuit, correspondence, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Transportation, Highways: 1969 Freeway Lawsuit, Memorandums, Report, Etc., 1968-1969 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Transportation, Highways: 1969 Freeway Lawsuit, NCPC Agendas, 1967-1968 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Transportation, Highways: North Leg, Appraisal and Acquisitions, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Transportation, Highways: North Leg, correspondence and resolution, 1960-1967 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Transportation, Highways: North Leg, News clippings, 1967-1972 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Transportation, Highways: North Leg, " Rehabilitation of Housing Report,", 1968 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Transportation, Highways: North Leg, Report, 1970 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Transportation, Highways: Preservation Along Highway Corridors, 1966-1981 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Transportation, Highways: Preservation Along Highway Corridors, 1962-1966 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Transportation, Highways: Property Acquisitions in D.C., 1967-1968 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Transportation, Highways: Publication, miscellaneous, 1966-1972 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Transportation, Highways: Reports on House Bill 16000, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Transportation, Highways: Roads Sub -Committee Materials, 1965-1970 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Transportation, Highways: Route 240 (Center Loop), miscellaneous material, 1964-1970 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Transportation, Highways: "Scenic Roads and Parkways Proposal," Dept. of Commerce, 1966 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Transportation, Highways: Statements and Resolutions, miscellaneous, 1961-1969 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Transportation, Highways: Statements and Resolutions, miscellaneous, 1970-1977 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Transportation, Highways: Traffic Volume Statistics, 1971-1973 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Administrative Remedies Often Need not be Exhausted, Law Policy Report, undated (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Marion Barry, correspondence and new clippings, 1987 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Highway Beautification, "Beautification Act of 1965," (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Highway Beautification, control of outdoor Advertising", 1965 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Highway Beautification, correspondence, 1964-1967 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Highway Beautification, correspondence on Billboards, 1960-1980 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Highway Beautification, Federal Highway Acts, 1959-1960 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Highway Beautification, news clippings on Billboards, 1965-1967 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Highway Beautification, Photographs with petition, 1958 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Highway Beautification, "Report on Sign regulations,", 1954 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Highway Beautification, "Roadside Development and Beautification" (NAS), 1965-1966 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Highway Proposals in N.Y. and Pennsylvania, reports, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Junior League Christmas Shop, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - News Clippings, 1962-1971 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Interactive Downtown Task Force (1 of 2), 1996-1997; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Interactive Downtown Task Force (2 of 2), 1996; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - C100 Statement on DC Law 8-358 Review of Resolution of 1990, Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Development plans, 1995-1997; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - C100 PIPA: Accounts General, 1972-1994; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - C100:PIPA Accounts (history), 1987-1995; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - C100: PIPA - AU (American University), 1991-1994; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - The Accokeek Foundation - Correspondence, 1994-1994; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - C100 PIPA Neighbors for Livable Communities, 1987-1992; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Appleseed Foundation, 1994-1995; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - The Chesapeake and Potomac Regional Alliance, 1995; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - News Articles: Congress - Related, 1995; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Richard Longstreath, undated; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Magazine: D.C. Board of Trade, 1990; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - D.C. Budget, 1993; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Washington Post: D.C. Chamber of Commerce, 1991; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Washington Post: Members of the D.C. Council, 1995; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - D.C. Statehood, 1978-1993; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - D.C. Watch, 1995; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Federal Facilities, 1991-1994; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - David H. Gleason Association, 1995; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - Home Rule: "Why the District's Home Rule is Useless: A Suburan View", 1995; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Urban Youth Leadership Initiative, unated; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - Washington Network, 1987-1988; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - Washington Regional Network for Livable Communities, 1995; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Historic Preservation: General - Churches, 1993-1994; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - Historic Preservation: General - Demotion by Neglect, 1990-1993; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 27)
  - Historic Preservation: General - Façade Projects, 1993; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 28)
  - Historic Preservation: General - Mall Memorials, 1987-1991; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 29)
  - Historic Preservation: General Main Street Program, 1995; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - Historic Preservation - General - Misc, 1985-1995; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 31)
  - Historic Preservation, 1991; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 32)